samplewonderlictest.com 2018-11-30

# Sample Wonderlic Test

Last updated May 24, 2018

We take your privacy seriously. This statement describes the privacy policy for our entire website, including the information we capture and how it is used. By using our website you accept the terms of this Privacy Policy.

We capture information from visitors in two different ways:        

  * Directly – through information you submit to us
  * Indirectly – through our website technology

## Direct Data Collection

Personal data is only stored when voluntarily given by you for a determined purpose e.g. in context of a registration, a survey, a contest or in performance of a contract.  Your individual, identifiable, personal data will not be disclosed to third parties, without your consent.

### Ecommerce

To purchase digital downloads you will be required to provide personally identifiable information, including payment details. We do not share this information with any third parties. Payment is facilitated through a secure payment processor and we do not store credit card information. All purchases are subject to Terms and Conditions.

## Indirect Data Collection

By using aggregate statistical analysis, we review trends based on information as a whole, but not so as to identify individual users. Data collected indirectly through the use of proprietary and/or third-party software technology may include, but is not limited to:

  * IP address
  * Domain name
  * Referral data and exit pages
  * Browser type
  * Operating system platform
  * Internet service provider
  * Date/time

We use this information to analyze trends, administer the site, track users' movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.

### Cookies

Cookies are small files of information that websites can store on your computer's hard drive.  We use cookies in order to assist in aggregate statistical analysis and sometimes provide site customization based on anonymous session tracking. Cookies cannot be used to determine the actual identity of users, but they can be used to identify a computer. If the site is customized based on cookies, we won't know who you are unless you tell us.

Cookies on Our Website

The list below summarizes the cookies on this website and the purposes for which they are used. For more information on changing your browser’s cookie settings, see “Managing Cookies” below.

**Name**

| 

**Source**

| 

**Purpose**  
  
---|---|---  
  
_ga, _gid

| 

Google Analytics

| 

Identifies a user for purposes of aggregate reporting and analytics on visits to this site.  
  
_gat

| 

Google Analytics

| 

Controls the frequency of requests to the Google Analytics service.  
  
_dm_sync

| 

Google DoubleClick for Publishers/ Google AdSense

| 

Allows for display of ads on this site.  
  
__gads

| 

Google DoubleClick for Publishers/ Google AdSense

| 

Measures interactions with the ads on this site.  
  
waldo_country

| 

Newor Media

|   
  
switch-synchronized

| 

Newor Media

| 

Allows for display of ads on this site.  
  
laravel_session

| 

First-party cookie

| 

Identifies a session instance for a user.  
  
XSRF-TOKEN

| 

First-party cookie

| 

Authenticates POST requests and prevents Cross Site Request Forgery (XSRF) attacks.  
  
Third Party Cookies

We may allow third parties, advertising companies, and ad networks, to display advertisements on our site. These companies may use tracking technologies, such as cookies, to collect information about users who view or interact with their advertisements. Our website does not provide any personal information to these third parties, but they may collect information about where you, or others who are using your computer, saw and/or clicked on the advertisements they deliver, and possibly associate this information with your subsequent visits to the advertised websites. They also may combine this information with personal information they collect from you. The collection and use of that information is subject to the third-party’s privacy policy. This information allows them to deliver targeted advertisements and gauge their effectiveness.

Managing Cookies

You may refuse to accept cookies by altering the settings on your internet browser (for example Internet Explorer, Chrome and Firefox). Please note that if you choose not to permit cookies some areas of our website may not function properly or be accessible.

For further information about how to refuse cookies, please refer to your browser ‘help’ section or see [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/).

### Web Beacons

Web beacons are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of web users or to access cookies. Unlike cookies, which are stored on the user’s computer hard drive, web beacons are embedded invisibly on the web pages (or in email) and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. Web beacons may be used to deliver or communicate with cookies, to count users who have visited certain pages and to understand usage patterns. We may include web beacons in promotional or other email messages or newsletters to determine whether messages have been opened and acted upon. If you come to our site from an online advertisement displayed on a third-party website, you may receive an anonymous identification number.

## Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA)

Protecting the privacy of young people is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we know to be under 13 and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.

## Links and Information Gathered by Others

Our site contains links to other sites. We do not operate these sites, cannot control what information such sites gather or what such sites do with the information, and is therefore not responsible for the activities of the operators of such sites. This privacy statement only applies to information collected by our site.

## NAI/IAB

We are compliant with the policies of several industry groups that focus on effective communication, best practices, and policy review in the field of Online Behavioral Advertising (OBA). These organizations include the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI), the Digital Advertising Alliance (DAA), and the Interactive Advertising Bureau (IAB). We are compliant with both the NAI and DAA self-regulatory codes. We believe that delivering targeted and relevant advertising enhances your internet experience. You can opt-out [here](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/).

## Data Removal Request

To receive a copy of your data or to have it removed, please submit your request in writing and we will act on it within 7 business days.

## Changes to the Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement or other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.

## Contact

If you have questions about our privacy practices, please contact us.
